revtrax.com 2017-06-25

# RevTrax | Acquire. Know. Grow.

### Terms of Use

**Welcome to our Terms of Use. OnCard Marketing, Inc., whose registered office is 132 West 31st Street, Suite 702, New York, NY 10001, ("OnCard," "us," "we" or "our") has created the following terms of use (the "Terms of Use") which govern your use of our websites,**[ **saveinstore.com**](https://www.saveinstore.com/) **,**[ **revtrax.com**](http://revtrax.com/) **,**[ **verifymycoupon.com**](http://verifymycoupon.com/vmc/qrverify.jsp) **and any other websites, software, applications and features that link to or incorporate this Terms of Use (the "Services"). Please read this Terms of Use agreement carefully.** **Your access and use of the Services means that you accept these Terms of Use.**

By accessing or using a Service, which includes any coupon, discount, promotion or other offer made available on or through the Services (each a "Promotion"), you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by this Terms of Use and our Privacy Policy

 _,_

which is incorporated into these Terms of Use. We may change the Terms of Use by posting revisions to this page. Your continued use of the Services means that you accept any and all revised terms.

**USER OBLIGATIONS AND RESPONSIBILITIES**

**You are responsible for your account.** If you register for an account with us, you must provide us with current, complete, and accurate registration information. You may be asked to choose a password and a user name. You are responsible for maintaining the currency, completeness, and accuracy of your registration data and the confidentiality of your user name, password and other account information. You are responsible for any and all activities that occur under your account. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your account. We are not liable for any loss that you may incur as a result of your failure to comply with these requirements or someone else using your password or account, either with or without your knowledge.  

**You are responsible for the information you enter and your compliance with laws and other terms.** You agree that: (a) you are a legal resident of the United States or Canada as indicated when you registered; (b) you are at or above the legal age of majority in your jurisdiction of residence; (c) you own or are authorized to use the computer, mobile device, technology or other device you use to access any of the Services; (d) all information entered by you into the Services is accurate and valid; (e) you will access and use the Services in accordance with these Terms of Use and any terms and conditions associated with specific Promotions; (f) you will utilize the Services and Promotions in accordance with all laws, regulations and privacy policies, this Terms of Use and the terms and conditions associated with each specific Promotion; (g) **** if you use PrintMyCoupon®, you will comply with the [End User License Agreement](http://www.revtrax.com/eula.php), which is incorporated into these Terms of Use; and (h) if you use any third party tool, service, software or application made available on or through the Services, including load to card, receipt upload or other reward programs or functionality, you will comply with the applicable third party terms and conditions. Click [here](https://www.cellfire.com/mobcx/tos.php) for links to applicable terms for load to card functionality.  

**PROHIBITED USES**

**You agree to use the Services only as permitted.** **Copying, scanning, selling, transferring, auctioning, reposting and any other unauthorized duplication or distribution of a Promotion is not permitted.** For clarity, this includes sales and transfers of Promotions in any form, including as PDFs, digitally or printed coupons via sites such as Instagram, eBay and Facebook and applies whether or not you charge a fee for the Promotions, charge for "your time or effort" or request a donation. Further, you agree to (i) not use multiple IP addresses, servers or email addresses to access additional Promotions for yourself or others, and (iii) not use any device, technology or other method to bypass print limits set for each Promotion. In addition to these restrictions, each Promotion has its own prohibitions with which you agree to comply.  

**You agree not to engage or attempt to engage in potentially harmful acts directed against our Services, Promotions or customers.**   
**This includes:**

  1. Violating or attempting to violate any security feature of the Services, including print limits;
  2. Interfering or attempting to interfere with the use of our Promotions, Services or network or systems, including by spamming or introducing a virus or other malicious code;
  3. Tampering with or modifying in any manner with (including functionality, operation, or security) the Services or any Promotion;
  4. Engaging in "mirroring," "framing" or otherwise simulating the appearance or function of the Services or any Promotion; and
  5. Hyperlinking to a Promotion or the Services from any other website without our prior written consent.

**You agree that violation of these Terms of Use causes significant harm.** You understand and acknowledge that unauthorized use, copying, sale, transfer or disclosure of the Promotions or Services will cause us, our customers and licensors irreparable injury, which may not be remedied at law, and you agree that our, our customers, our vendors and our licensors' remedies for breach of these Terms of Use include injunctive or other equitable relief and such equitable remedies can be pursued without the posting of a bond or without necessity for proving monetary damages by the injured party.  

**OWNERSHIP RIGHTS**

**We own what is on our Services.** All content and materials on or related to our Promotions and Services, including, but not limited to, trade names, logos, trademarks, service marks, trade dress, copyrights, software, images, audio, video, photographs, forms, data, text, graphics, icons, and other information and material ("Service Content") are our property or the property of our customers, vendors, partners or licensors, and is protected by copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets, patents and/or other intellectual property rights. All Service Content is copyright protected as individual works and as a collective work under copyright laws and pursuant to international treaties. We own a copyright in the arrangement, selection, coordination and enhancement of the Service Content. You understand and agree that these rights are valid and protected in all media, forms and technologies existing now or hereinafter developed. You further acknowledge and agree that we own and shall retain all right, title and interest in the (a) Service Content, (b) bar codes, designs, ideas, processes, methodologies, forms and formats, materials, software, Internet domain names, arrangement of content, distinctive and original layout and presentation on or related to the Promotions or Services, and (c) derivative works or enhancements to any of the foregoing.  

**You agree to certain limitations on your use of our Services.** You may not, and agree that you will not, reproduce, download, license, publish, enter into a database, display, modify, create derivative works from, transmit, post, distribute or perform publicly by any means, method, or process now known or later developed, decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, use on another computer-related environment, transfer or sell any Service Content, Promotions, Services or information obtained from or through the Services, in whole or in part, without our express written permission or as expressly authorized on the Services.  

**WARRANTIES, DISCLAIMERS, INDEMNIFICATION AND RELEASE**  

THE PROMOTIONS AND SERVICES (INCLUDING ALL SOFTWARE ACCESSIBLE THEREFROM) ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. WE MAKE NO WARRANTY THAT THE PROMOTIONS OR SERVICES: (A) WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS OR EXPECTATIONS, OR (B) WILL BE AVAILABLE ON AN UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE BASIS.  

YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT WITH RESPECT TO THE SERVICES AND ALL THIRD PARTY TOOLS, CONTENT, SOFTWARE AND SERVICES ACCESSIBLE THEREFROM ("THIRD PARTY CONTENT"), WE SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT AND ANY IMPLIED WARRANTY ARISING FROM COURSE OF PERFORMANCE, COURSE OF DEALING OR USAGE OF TRADE.  

YOU AGREE TO ASSUME SOLE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR USE OF THE PROMOTIONS, THE SERVICES, AND ANY MATERIAL DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THE SERVICES, INCLUDING ALL THIRD PARTY CONTENT. YOU AGREE THE SERVICES ARE ACCESSED AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK, AND YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR AND HEREBY WAIVE ANY AND ALL CLAIMS AND CAUSES OF ACTION WITH RESPECT TO ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR INTERNET ACCESS, COMPUTER FUNCTIONALITY, DEVICE, OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM SUCH DOWNLOAD, ACCESS OR USE. WE ALSO SHALL HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER, DEVICE, SYSTEMS OR ANY LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM YOUR USE OF THE PROMOTIONS OR SERVICES, INCLUDING ANY THIRD PARTY CONTENT.  

In no event shall we, our affiliates, clients, vendors, partners, licensors, agents or others involved in creating, sponsoring, promoting, or otherwise making available the Services, the Service Contents, or the Promotions, be liable to any person or entity whatsoever for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, compensatory, consequential, or punitive damages or any damages whatsoever, including but not limited to: (i) loss of goodwill, profits, business interruption, data or other intangible losses; (ii) your inability to use, performance or non-performance of the Services; (iii) unauthorized access to or tampering with the Services and Promotions, including your personal information or transmissions; (iv) the provision or failure to provide any Service; (v) errors or inaccuracies contained on this Service; (vi) any transactions entered into through this Services; (vii) any property damage including damage to your computer system caused by viruses or other harmful components, during or on account of access to or use of the Services or any site to or from which it hyperlinks or any or Third Party Content; or (viii) damages otherwise arising out of the use of the Services or Third Party Content. The limitations of liability shall apply regardless of the form of action, whether based on contract, tort, negligence, strict liability or otherwise, even if we or any third party has been advised of the possibility of damage.  
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless us, our agents, clients, vendors, partners licensors and affiliates, and their respective officers, directors and employees from and against any and all claims, actions, demands, liabilities, costs and expenses, including, without limitation, reasonable attorneys fees, resulting from your breach of any provision of this Agreement, or otherwise arising in any way out of your use of the Services or the Promotions. You agree to cooperate fully with us in asserting any available defenses in connection with a claim subject to indemnification by you under this Agreement.  

SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE DISCLAIMER OR EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES OR THE DISCLAIMER OR EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN LIABILITIES, SO SOME OF THE ABOVE DISCLAIMERS OR EXCLUSIONS OR LIMITATIONS OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IF ANY OF THE PROVISIONS OF THESE TERMS OF USE ARE HELD BY A COURT OR OTHER TRIBUNAL OF COMPETENT JURISDICTION TO BE VOID OR UNENFORCEABLE, SUCH PROVISIONS SHALL BE LIMITED OR ELIMINATED TO THE MINIMUM EXTENT NECESSARY AND REPLACED WITH A VALID PROVISION THAT BEST EMBODIES THE INTENT OF THESE TERMS OF USE AND THESE TERMS OF USE SHALL REMAIN IN FULL FORCE AND EFFECT.  

IF YOU ARE A CALIFORNIA RESIDENT, YOU WAIVE SECTION 1542 OF THE CALIFORNIA CIVIL CODE, WHICH SAYS: "A GENERAL RELEASE DOES NOT EXTEND TO CLAIMS WHICH THE CREDITOR DOES NOT KNOW OR SUSPECT TO EXIST IN HIS FAVOR AT THE TIME OF EXECUTING THE RELEASE, WHICH, IF KNOWN BY HIM MUST HAVE MATERIALLY AFFECTED HIS SETTLEMENT WITH THE DEBTOR."  

**THIRD PARTY SITES AND VENDORS**

**The products advertised through Promotions are offered by third parties, not us.** The purchase, use of and all other matters concerning the products are solely between you and such businesses. We do not endorse, warrant or guarantee such products, and are not responsible nor liable for the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of Service Content related to such products.   
**We have no responsibility for the content of the linked site(s)** **or Third Party Content.** The Services may also include links to other sites and or Third Party Content. We do not endorse or make any representations or warranties regarding the site(s) or Third Party Content.  
**When you use a third party service available on or through the Services, you agree to the third partys terms and conditions.** We or our customers may use, partner with or allow third party email, loyalty card, receipt upload, printing, SMS or other vendors to access, distribute, activate or redeem the Promotions and Services. You are responsible for reviewing and understanding the privacy and other policies of the applicable third parties. You understand that SMS Promotions may be subject to standard data and other fees from your mobile or SMS provider.  

**GENERAL TERMS:**   
**We may use information collected.** The Services use cookies and other technologies. We may use information in various ways, including to enhance your experience on the Services, to recognize you so that you will not have to re-enter information during your current or future visit to the Services, and to provide you with Promotions based on information you provided or your prior activity on the Services or with our clients, vendors or partners. The collection and use of information is governed by our [Privacy Policy](). You may opt out of interest-based behavioral advertising [here](http://www.revtrax.com/opt-out.php).  

**You agree that these Terms of Use are a valid, binding contract between you and us.** You agree that the Terms of Use comply with applicable contractual, statutory, and other legal requirements and are legally enforceable as a signed writing against you. If any portion of this Terms of Use is held invalid, you agree that such invalidity will not affect the validity of the remaining portions of the Terms of Use. No waiver by us of any breach or default of this Terms of Use will constitute a continuing waiver of the breach or default or be deemed to be a waiver of any prior or subsequent breach or default. The Terms of Use represents the complete agreement between us and you regarding the Services, Promotions and Services and supersedes all prior agreements and representations between us and you.  

**JURISDICTION**   

**You agree to binding arbitration and waive rights to participate in a class action.** Any dispute relating in any way to your use of the Promotions and Services shall be submitted to confidential arbitration in New York, New York, except that, to the extent you have in any manner violated or threatened to violate our intellectual property rights, we may seek injunctive or other appropriate relief in any state or federal court in the state of New York. Arbitration under this Agreement shall be conducted under the rules then prevailing of the American Arbitration Association. The arbitrator's award shall be binding and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, no arbitration under this Agreement shall be joined to an arbitration involving any other party subject to this Agreement, whether through class arbitration proceedings or otherwise, and you agree that you will not participate as a class member or class representative in any action against us.  

**The Terms of Use and your use of the Promotions and Services are governed by and subject to the laws of the State of New York, without regard to its conflict of laws provisions. To the extent any claim is brought before a court of law, you irrevocably and unconditionally agree to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located in New York, New York for all matters arising out of these Terms of Use and your use of the Promotions and Services and waive all rights to a jury trial.**   

**QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION**   

Questions regarding these Terms of Use can be addressed to:  
OnCard Marketing, Inc.  
132 West 31st Street, Suite 702  
New York, NY 10001  
Attn: Legal Dept. Privacy Officer or [privacy@revtrax.com](mailto:privacy@revtrax.com)   
_Last Modified: 03/02/17_

* * *

### Privacy Policy

**1\. Overview**  
OnCard Marketing, Inc. d/b/a RevTrax ("RevTrax", "us" or "we") respects your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Policy describes our policies and practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of information we collect via websites, services, mobile and software applications we own, operate or control and coupons powered by us, including emails and certain portions of third party websites and applications that link to this Privacy Policy (the "Services"). Our Services may include links to and content and tools from third-party websites and services. Any third party's collection and use of your information is governed by their privacy policy and terms. We recommend you review the privacy policies and terms of those third parties. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Also, please review our Terms of Use. When you use or interact with the Services, you consent to the collection and use of information as set forth in this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.   
Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Notice, please contact us at [privacy@revtrax.com](mailto:privacy@revtrax.com) or contact us in writing at:  
RevTrax  
132 West 31st Street, Suite 702  
New York, NY 10001  
Attn: Legal Dept - Privacy Officer

**2\. Updates to Our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time to incorporate changes to our practices, so please review it periodically. The date of the most current revisions will be reflected by the "Last Modified" notice below. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you via email or provide notice on or through the Services prior to the change becoming effective. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SITES OR SERVICES CONSTITUTES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.   
Click on one of the links below to jump to the listed section: 

  1. Overview
  2. Updates to Our Privacy Policy
  3. Information We Collect
  4. How We Use Information
  5. Sharing of Information
  6. Other Sites
  7. Protecting Your Information
  8. Your Privacy Choices; Access
  9. Interest Based Advertising; Opt-Out
  10. Children's Privacy
  11. California Do Not Track Disclosures
  12. Your California Privacy Rights
  13. Note for International Users

**3\. Information We Collect**

_Information You Provide_

When you use the Services, we may ask you to provide information that can be used to personally identify, contact or locate you, such as your name, email address, phone number or home address ('Personal Information'). For clarity, Personal Information does not include information that has been made anonymous, such as a unique identifier, or aggregated in a manner that renders it unable to be used to personally identify, contact or locate you. It will always be your choice whether or not to directly provide us your Personal Information. You may also provide us with information about yourself or your household that may be associated with your Personal Information. We may collect any information, whether or not personally identifiable, that you choose to provide, subject to applicable laws and the terms of this Privacy Policy.

We may request or collect information in many ways, including when: (a) you register for Services; (b) you request a promotion or other Services that requires you to enter information such as a mobile phone number, loyalty identifier or email address; (c) you participate in a social sharing promotion or survey; (d) you submit questions or requests to our customer service and other contacts; (e) you interact with our Services via a social networking platform; (g) you post content to our Services; (g) you enter a contest or sweepstakes; (h) you participate in a receipt upload, loyalty card, or other incentive program; or (i) you use other features of the Services. 

_Information We Collect Automatically_

Whenever you use or interact with the Services, we use technologies that automatically or passively collect information about how the Services are accessed and used ('Usage Information'). Usage Information helps us keep the Services up to date and allows us to tailor our content to your interests, among other things. Usage Information may include: promotion views, activations and interactions, which brands and types of promotions you have engaged with, number of times you have used the Services, the website that referred you to us and any other information passed in the referral header URL such as search terms you used, the web pages you viewed on the Services, cookies, IP address or other unique identifiers, browser information, operating system, mobile device identifiers, information about use of mobile applications, the geographic location of a device and the dates and times that you used the Services. User Information may be associated with Personal Information or an anonymous identifier.   

_Information Collected from Third Parties_

Information, including Personal Information, may be collected by our clients or third-party vendors and provided to us in conjunction with our Services. This information may include the location, business name, date, and/or time the promotion was redeemed, in addition to other online and offline transaction details. We also allow third-party companies to use cookies, pixels or other similar technologies on our Services to collect and use non-personally identifiable information, including cookie identifiers, hashed information, browser and clickstream data. These third parties include advertisers, service providers, ad networks and other third parties with whom we or our clients partner to provide you with the Services. These third parties may use technologies to provide you with advertisements, including interest-based advertising, track offline transactions and to assist us in providing and improving the Services. These third parties may combine the data they collect from these technologies with other data they collect. You should review the privacy policies of these parties. To learn about interest-based advertising and understand your choices regarding third party cookies, [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers).

_Information Collected Through Tracking Technologies_

We use cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies in our Services to track and understand the use of our Services, personalize experiences and for research and marketing as further discussed below.

_Cookies and Flash Cookies_ \- Cookies and Flash Cookies are small data files (text or alphanumeric strings) placed on a computer, mobile device, browser, application, technology or other device when the Services are accessed to collect and store certain information about your interactions. Cookies also allow us to provide you with additional promotions that are most likely to appeal to you based on your use of the Services. We may use session cookies and persistent cookies. Persistent cookies remain after you close your browser. To personalize your experience, Services may utilize third-party technologies, such as plug-ins, that use local shared objects, also known as Flash Cookies or HTML5, to store information, including your preferences or to display customized content based upon what you view on our Services, including certain types of advertising. Flash Cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. You always have the option to [disable browser cookies using standard methods for your browser](https://www.google.com/#q=how+to+clear+browser+cookies).Cookie management tools provided by your browser may not remove Flash Cookies. To learn how to disable and manage cookies and Flash Cookies, please [click here](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). Please be aware that disabling these functions may negatively impact your use and enjoyment of the Services, including preventing you from viewing or activating a promotion.

_Pixels and Web Beacons_ \- We may also include small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags, tracking beacons and clear GIFs) on the Services). Web beacons, pixels or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including without limitation, to obtain information such as the URL of the page on which the beacon appears or the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, to measure promotion effectiveness through the Services, or to optimize promotion performance. Pixels and web beacons may also be placed by third parties on the Services. This privacy policy does not govern the use of such third party pixels and web beacons.

_Unique Identifiers_ \- A Unique Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your interaction with the Services when you access a web site or its servers. Our systems may identify your interaction by a Unique Identifier. A Unique Identifier may be associated with your IP address, device ID or other unique identifier. A Unique Identifier may be used and identify your interactions across channels, devices and/or brands.

_Executable File_ \- An Executable File is a downloadable software application file that contains instructions that perform tasks on a computer. We may use an Executable File to control the activation of a promotion.

_Java Applet_ \- A Java Applet is a downloadable software file that contains instructions that perform tasks on a computer initiated by your web browser. We may use a Java Applet to control the print limits of a promotion.

_Third Party Persistent Cookie - Analytics_   
We may use proprietary and third party tracking analytics and tools to better understand how the Services are used and by whom. One service provider, Google Analytics, places persistent cookies on your computer to analyze your behavior on your visit to this website as well as on other websites, enabling us to improve your experience on the Services. To opt out of the Google Analytics collection of information, use this link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

**4\. How We Use Information**

We use information we collect for a variety of business purposes, including to: provide and improve the Services and services to our Clients; administrative purposes such as the maintenance and operation of the Services or to respond to requests that you make; provide you with a personalized experience on and off the Services, including advertising and promotions; and create and utilize metrics, analytics and data related to the Services. We also use information to comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent fraud (including by preventing access to promotions if you have violated our [Terms of Use]()), and enforce agreements and the terms of our Services, including our Terms of Use.

We may combine data we collect from different sources, including information obtained from third parties, across Services and devices. We may use information collected to provide you with a personalized experience on the Services, such as providing you with coupons or other offers based on your interests and using information from your past usage of the Services in order to present or send you notifications of new offers that may be relevant to you.   
Your IP address may be used to identify or customize promotions for you by geographic location. In addition, we may also use information to help our clients, partners and vendors improve their services, communicate with you about promotions that may be of interest to you, prevent fraud and over-redemption and for other promotional and business purposes in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**5\. Sharing of Information**

Except as described here, we will not provide any of your Personal Information to any third parties without your consent. We may share non-Personal Information, such as aggregate data, anonymous identifiers, Usage Information, age, gender, zip code, marital status and similar information with third parties. We may share your feedback and comments on our Services with third parties. We may also share your information as follows:

_Third Parties:_ We may share your information, including Personal Information, with third parties that sponsor or participate in promotions through our Services, or that perform functions on our behalf, such as service providers that host or operate our Services, analyze data, administer our promotions, email, text, survey, sweepstakes and other Services, provide customer service, make various features, content and rewards available to you on or through the Services, such as load to card and receipt upload, or respond to your inquiries. These parties will be authorized to use the information in accordance with the terms of their participation in the Services, but they may also combine information we provide with information they have about you. For example, a reward program provider will receive the information necessary to verify your participation and apply your reward. We may also share the non-Personal Information we collect through the Services with partners such as advertisers, agencies, ad networks, data management platforms or exchanges to enable them to analyze user behaviors or to customize the ads that you encounter. We may also share information with third parties to obtain associated information, including cookies and other identifiers, and for advertising and marketing, including targeting advertisements on the Services or third party websites. To learn about targeted advertising, [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers) and to opt-out of certain advertising, [click here](http://www.revtrax.com/opt-out.php). 

_With Your Consent_ : While using or accessing our Services, you may have the opportunity to agree to receive information and/or marketing offers from someone else, to share your information with a third party, or to participate in or be linked with a third-party program, such as a brand email, store loyalty card or reward program. If you agree to have your Personal Information shared, use a feature or participate in a program powered by, accessed through or in partnership with a third party, your Personal Information may be disclosed to the third party and will be subject to the privacy policy and business practices of that third party.

_Business Transfers:_ We may share your Personal Information with other entities and our affiliates primarily for business and operational purposes. In the event that we are involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, we reserve the right to sell or transfer your information as part of that transaction. 

_Legal Disclosure:_ We may transfer and disclose your information to third parties to comply with a legal obligation; when we believe in good faith that the law or a governmental authority requires it; to verify or enforce our agreements, Terms of Use or other applicable policies; to address fraud, security or technical issues; to respond to an emergency; or otherwise to protect our rights or property or security of third parties, users of the Services or the public.  

**6\. Other Sites**

The Services may contain links to and cookies, pixels and web beacons from other sites that we do not own or operate, including from clients, advertisers or partners. We do not control, recommend or endorse and are not responsible for these sites or their content, products, services, privacy policies or practices. These other sites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit Personal Information and have their own privacy policies.  

**7\. Protecting Your Information**

We use various physical, administrative and technical security measures to help protect your Personal Information. No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network, nor any data storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we try to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, nor do we warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.  

**8\. Your Privacy Choices; Access**

Keeping Personal Information about you current helps ensure that we offer you the best promotions available through our clients and partners. You can access, update and delete the information you provided in your SaveInStore® account by logging in and going to your My Account page, using the applicable features in other Services or contacting us at [privacy@revtrax.com](mailto:privacy@revtrax.com). We will retain your information (including geo-location data) for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you the Services or longer as permitted by law. We may also retain and use copies of your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.  

**9\. Interest-Based Advertising Opt-Out**   

To opt out of certain interest-based behaviorally targeted promotions and advertising for this browser served by us or on our behalf, [click here](http://www.revtrax.com/opt-out.php).   

If you opt out of behavioral advertising using the above tool, you will still see Promotions and online advertisements served on our behalf, but those will not be personalized based on your interaction with the Services or other information we have about you. In addition, after you opt out, the Services may still collect information about your use of the Services, including for analytics, fraud prevention and any other business purposes permitted in this Privacy Policy.   

Please also note that the opt-out mechanism above must be selected for each browser you use. Also, if you delete the cookies in your browser your advertising preferences will be reset for that browser and you will need to opt out again.  

For more information about cookies and interest-based advertising, see information from the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/obaprinciples) and [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising). You can also visit [Facebook's ad preferences tool](https://www.facebook.com/help/247395082112892). You can learn about your choices to opt out of mobile app tracking through your device settings and by resetting your advertiser ID on your Apple or Android devices.   

**10\. Children's Privacy**

The Sites and the Services are not directed to children under 13. However, protecting the privacy of young children is especially important to us. As such, we do not knowingly collect, maintain or use information from anyone under 13 years of age. If we learn Personal Information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected by the Services, we will take the necessary steps to delete the information. If you are under 13 years of age, use or access of the Services at any time or in any manner is strictly prohibited.  

**11\. California Do Not Track Disclosures**

We may collect information about users over time and across different websites when you use the Services. There may also be third parties that collect information this way. The Services do not currently respond to "Do Not Track" browser signals or mechanisms. However, other settings within your browser may permit you to block cookies or use other technologies that enable websites to collect information that can be used to tailor advertisements to your interest. We offer an opt-out from interest-based behavioral advertising through our Services [here](http://www.revtrax.com/opt-out.php)..  

**12\. Your California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California resident, under California's "Shine the Light" law you may have the right to request and receive certain information about our disclosure of your Personal Information to third parties for their own marketing use, and your choices with respect to such disclosures once per year. If applicable, this information would include the types of customer information and the businesses with which we shared your customer information for the prior calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to request a copy of this information, please submit a request to us at the address provided in the Overview section above to the attention of "Legal Department." In your request, please specify that you want a "Your California Privacy Rights Notice." Please allow 30 days for a response.

**Note for International Users**

Although the Services may be accessed from any country via the Internet, [www.SaveInStore.com](http://www.saveinstore.com/) and all content and related Services is only directed to U.S. citizens residing in the U.S. Other Sites and Services may have content directed to both U.S. and Canadian citizens dwelling in those countries.

THE SERVICES ARE HOSTED IN THE UNITED STATES. IF YOU ARE NOT A U.S. CITIZEN OR ACCESSING THE SITES FROM ANY OTHER COUNTRY, PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT THROUGH YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES WHICH IS GOVERNED BY U.S. LAW AND THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IN DOING SO, YOU ARE TRANSFERRING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE U.S. AND YOU CONSENT TO THAT TRANSFER AND THE TERMS OF U.S. LAWS AND THIS PRIVACY POLICY. Furthermore, by accessing or using the Services, or providing us with any information, you consent to the collection, processing, maintenance and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other applicable territories in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as or equivalent to, those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen.

_Last Modified: 03/02/17_
